"use strict";(globalThis.webpackChunkfirecracker=globalThis.webpackChunkfirecracker||[]).push([[6976],{"./components/BarChartExitPolls/2022/ExitPolls.stories.js":(ee,v,l)=>{l.r(v),l.d(v,{NationalExitPollSubsets:()=>ye,NationalPage:()=>he,StatePage:()=>ve,SubsetsWithActiveDemographic:()=>me,__namedExportsOrder:()=>Te,default:()=>We});var b=l("./node_modules/@babel/runtime/helpers/esm/extends.js"),o=l("./node_modules/next/dist/compiled/react/index.js"),s=l("./components/BarChartExitPolls/primaries/index.js"),w=l("./node_modules/prop-types/index.js"),e=l.n(w),i=l("./node_modules/next/amp.js"),B=l("./node_modules/classnames/index.js"),t=l.n(B),x=l("./node_modules/styled-jsx/style.js"),u=l.n(x),I=l("./helpers/color.js"),q=o.createElement;const M=({candidates:c})=>c.length?q(o.Fragment,null,q(u(),{id:"4027083565"},[".ep-candidate-legend.jsx-4027083565{min-height:16px;}",".color-swatch.jsx-4027083565{height:16px;width:16px;margin-top:1px;background:var(--candidate-color);}"]),q("ul",{className:"jsx-4027083565 ep-candidate-legend df flex-wrap lst-none pl0 mv0 justify-end"},c.map(({label:h,color:p})=>q("li",{key:`exit-poll__key--${h}`,"data-testid":`exit-poll__key--${p}`,className:"jsx-4027083565 df ep-candidate items-center mb2 mb1-m ml6"},q("span",{"data-testid":"key__color-swatch",style:{"--candidate-color":(0,I.convertToHex)(p)},className:"jsx-4027083565 color-swatch mr2 dib"}),q("span",{"data-testid":"exit-poll_key-label",className:"jsx-4027083565 founders-mono f2 lh-none fw4 gray-100 mv0 dib"},h))))):null;M.propTypes={candidates:e().arrayOf(e().shape({color:e().string,label:e().string}))},M.defaultProps={candidates:[]};const k=M;var E=l("./components/BarChartExitPolls/ExitPollPicker.js"),R=o.createElement;const z=({children:c})=>R("div",{className:"df row-wrapper"},c);z.displayName="Row";const H=z;var g=l("./components/BarChartExitPolls/Layout/LeftColumn.js"),S=l("./components/BarChartExitPolls/Layout/RightColumn.js"),d=l("./components/providers/StickyContext.js"),f=l("./components/props/exitPolls.propsShape.js"),O=l("./components/BarChartExitPolls/ExitPollsSubsets.js"),a=o.createElement;const U=({activeSubset:c,onSubsetChange:h,subsets:p,pollsByState:N,candidates:X,lastUpdated:C,showExitPollPicker:G,pollName:Y,isNational:J})=>{const{topNoMargin:y,topNoMarginM:m}=(0,d.useSticky)(),D=!(0,i.useAmp)()&&Array.isArray(p)&&!!p.length;return a(o.Fragment,null,a(u(),{id:"3376036635",dynamic:[y,m]},[`.exit-poll__candidates-key.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector{top:${y}px;}`,".ep-last-updated.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector{text-align:right;padding-top:8px;}",".with-subsets.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector .subsets-container{-webkit-flex:1;-ms-flex:1;flex:1;}",".with-subsets.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector .legend.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector{-webkit-flex:1;-ms-flex:1;flex:1;}",`@media only screen and (min-width:758px){.exit-poll__candidates-key.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector{top:${m}px;}}`]),a("div",{"data-testid":"exit-polls__sticky-header",className:u().dynamic([["3376036635",[y,m]]])+" "+(t()("sticky bg-white z-2 exit-poll__candidates-key pb2")||"")},G&&!!N.length&&a(H,null,a(g.default,null,a("div",{"data-testid":"exit-poll__picker",className:u().dynamic([["3376036635",[y,m]]])+" founders-cond gray-100 f4 lh-title fw4 pv3 tr-m pr2-m pb0-m"},"View other exit polls:")),a(S.default,null,a(E.default,{pollsByState:N,pollName:Y}))),a("div",{className:u().dynamic([["3376036635",[y,m]]])+" "+(t()("df justify-between-m",{"flex-column flex-row-m":!D,"with-subsets items-center flex-row":D})||"")},a("div",{className:u().dynamic([["3376036635",[y,m]]])+" "+(t()({dn:J&&D})||"")},!J&&C&&a("div",{className:u().dynamic([["3376036635",[y,m]]])+" ep-last-updated pv0-m founders-mono gray-80 f3 lh-copy fw4 mr2"},"Updated at ",C)),D&&a(O.default,{activeSubset:c,subsets:p,onChange:h}),a("div",{className:u().dynamic([["3376036635",[y,m]]])+" legend pt2"},a(k,{candidates:X})))))};U.propTypes={activeSubset:e().number,onSubsetChange:e().func,subsets:e().arrayOf(f.StateExitPollSubsetOption),lastUpdated:e().string,candidates:e().arrayOf(e().shape({color:e().string,label:e().string})),pollsByState:e().arrayOf(e().any),showExitPollPicker:e().bool},U.defaultProps={activeSubset:0,onSubsetChange:()=>{},subsets:null,pollsByState:[],candidates:[],lastUpdated:null,showExitPollPicker:!1};const P=U;var $=l("./components/HorizontalLabeledStackedBarChart/2022/index.js"),W=o.createElement;const j=({children:c})=>W(o.Fragment,null,W(u(),{id:"51192607"},[".ep-left-column.jsx-51192607{-webkit-flex:0 0 43%;-ms-flex:0 0 43%;flex:0 0 43%;}","@media only screen and (min-width:758px){.ep-left-column.jsx-51192607{-webkit-flex:0 0 30%;-ms-flex:0 0 30%;flex:0 0 30%;}}"]),W("div",{className:"jsx-51192607 ep-left-column w-30-m"},c));var F=o.createElement;const T=({children:c})=>F(o.Fragment,null,F(u(),{id:"3768577086"},[".ep-right-column.jsx-3768577086{-webkit-flex:0 0 57%;-ms-flex:0 0 57%;flex:0 0 57%;}","@media only screen and (min-width:758px){.ep-right-column.jsx-3768577086{-webkit-flex:0 0 70%;-ms-flex:0 0 70%;flex:0 0 70%;}}"]),F("div",{className:"jsx-3768577086 ep-right-column w-70-m"},c));var oe=l("./components/LinklessButton.js"),we=l("./components/icons/Chevron.js"),ge=l("./components/ScrollableTable/AmpCollapsibleWrapper/index.js"),n=o.createElement;const ne=({activeSubset:c,hideNegativeValues:h,subsets:p,onSubsetChange:N,lastUpdated:X,pollsByState:C,candidates:G,polls:Y,pollName:J,showExitPollPicker:y,resultsNotYetIn:m,maxPollsShown:Q,isNational:D,hasMulti:ue})=>{const{0:V,1:ie}=(0,o.useState)(!1),Ee=(0,i.useAmp)();if(!Y.length)return null;const pe=A=>!D&&A>=Q&&!V,be=()=>{ie(!V)},te=Y.map((A,Z)=>{const Be=A.id??`${A.question}-${Z}`;return n("div",{className:t()("ep-question-block pv3",{hidden:pe(Z)}),key:`exit-poll-question__${Be}`,"data-testid":"exit-polls__questions"},n(H,null,n("h5",{className:"founders-cond f6 lh-none fw6 gray-100 mv2"},A.question)),A.answers.map((_,Ie)=>h&&_.percent==="-1%"?null:n(H,{key:`exit-poll-${A.id}__${_.label}`},n(j,null,n("div",{className:"publico-txt f3 lh-title fw4 gray-100 mr2 mt3","data-testid":"exit-polls__labels"},_.label," (",_.percent||"0%",")")),n(T,null,n($.default,{values:_.values,showLegend:!1,key:`${A.id}--${A.answer}`,resultsNotYetIn:m,showResultsNotInLabel:Ie===0,height:"25px",textSize:"16px",isTwoBarSplit:G.length===2,hasSmallValueTextShadow:!0,hideSmallBarText:!1,isExitPolls:!0,addMargin:!1})))))}),ce=V?"show fewer":"show all",de=ue?ce:`${ce} ${J} exit polls`;return n(o.Fragment,null,n(u(),{id:"3117497253"},[".ep-question-block{border-bottom:dashed 1px #ccc;padding-bottom:24px;}",".ep-question-block:last-child{border:none;}",".hidden{display:none;}",".exit-polls__show-all-btn.is-open .chevron{-webkit-transform:rotate(180deg);-ms-transform:rotate(180deg);transform:rotate(180deg);}"]),n(P,{activeSubset:c,subsets:p,onSubsetChange:N,lastUpdated:X,candidates:G,pollsByState:C,showExitPollPicker:y,pollName:J,isNational:D}),D?te:n(ge.default,{defaultNumberOfRows:3,pluralReportingText:"Exit Polls",id:"exit-polls"},te),!Ee&&!D&&Y.length>Q&&n("div",{className:"jsx-3117497253 "+(t()("exit-polls__show-all-btn tc mv4",{"is-open":V})||"")},n(oe.default,{onClick:be},n("span",{className:"jsx-3117497253 dib ph6 pv2 ttu"},n("span",{"data-testid":"exit-polls__toggle-button",className:"jsx-3117497253 pr1"},de),n(we.default,{color:"#3061FF"})))))};ne.propTypes={activeSubset:e().number,hideNegativeValues:e().bool,onSubsetChange:e().func,subsets:e().arrayOf(f.StateExitPollSubsetOption),lastUpdated:e().string,pollsByState:e().arrayOf(e().any),candidates:e().arrayOf(e().any),polls:e().arrayOf(e().any),pollName:e().string,resultsNotYetIn:e().bool,showExitPollPicker:e().bool,maxPollsShown:e().number,isNational:e().bool,hasMulti:e().bool},ne.defaultProps={activeSubset:0,hideNegativeValues:!1,onSubsetChange:()=>{},subsets:null,lastUpdated:null,pollsByState:[],candidates:[],polls:[],pollName:"",resultsNotYetIn:!1,showExitPollPicker:!1,maxPollsShown:3,isNational:!1,hasMulti:!1};const fe=ne;var Ae=l("./components/Module.js"),qe=l("./components/SectionHeader.js"),Ne=l("./components/ModuleDescription.js"),xe=l("./components/PageAnchor/index.js"),L=o.createElement;const ae=({candidates:c,description:h,exitPollsNotClosedText:p,hideModule:N,hideNegativeValues:X,isNational:C,lastUpdated:G,linkText:Y,linkUrl:J,maxPollsShown:y,activeSubset:m,onSubsetChange:Q,subsets:D,pollName:ue,polls:V,pollsByState:ie,resultsNotYetIn:Ee,showExitPollPicker:pe,showPollsNotClosedText:be,showSectionHeader:te,title:ce,hasMulti:de})=>{const A=(0,i.useAmp)();if(N)return null;const Z=!A&&Array.isArray(D)&&!!D.length;return L(Ae.default,{testId:"exit-polls"},L(xe.default,{id:"exit-polls",title:"Exit polls"}),te&&L(qe.default,{headlineText:ce,linkText:Y,linkUrl:J,useHorizontalRule:!1,headlineSize:2,isNational:C,hasLinkWithChevron:!0,font:"founders-cond"}),L(Ne.default,null,h),L("div",{className:t()("ep-chart-container pb4",{pt2:!Z,pt6:Z})},be?L("div",{className:t()("founders-cond lh-none fw6 gray-100",{f8:C,f5:!C}),"data-testid":"exit-polls__polls-not-closed-text"},p):L(fe,{activeSubset:m,subsets:D,onSubsetChange:Q,lastUpdated:G,pollsByState:ie,candidates:c,polls:V,resultsNotYetIn:Ee,selectedPoll:ue,showExitPollPicker:pe,maxPollsShown:y,pollName:ue,isNational:C,hideNegativeValues:X,hasMulti:de})))};ae.displayName="ExitPollsModule2022",ae.propTypes={activeSubset:e().number,candidates:e().arrayOf(e().any),description:e().string,exitPollsNotClosedText:e().string,hideModule:e().bool,hideNegativeValues:e().bool,lastUpdated:e().string,linkText:e().string,linkUrl:e().string,maxPollsShown:e().number,onSubsetChange:e().func,pollName:e().string,polls:e().arrayOf(e().any),pollsByState:e().arrayOf(e().any),resultsNotYetIn:e().bool,showExitPollPicker:e().bool,showSectionHeader:e().bool,subsets:e().arrayOf(f.StateExitPollSubsetOption),title:e().string,hasMulti:e().bool},ae.defaultProps={activeSubset:0,candidates:[],description:null,exitPollsNotClosedText:"Check back when polls close for exit poll results",hideModule:!0,hideNegativeValues:!1,lastUpdated:null,linkText:null,linkUrl:null,maxPollsShown:null,onSubsetChange:()=>{},pollName:null,polls:[],pollsByState:[],resultsNotYetIn:!1,showExitPollPicker:!1,showSectionHeader:!0,subsets:null,title:"Exit Polls",hasMulti:!1};const Pe=ae,De=JSON.parse(`{"nationalPageDefault":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 P.M. ET.","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":5},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Category 2 Which has really long text that will porbably wrap","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":2},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":98},{"color":"#DE3535","value":1}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"Which best describes your education? You have:","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":0},{"color":"#DE3535","value":0},{"color":"#A99369","value":0},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":0}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Biden","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Trump","color":"DE3535"}],"pollsByState":[{"stateName":"National Presidential","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Arizona","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"California","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Colorado","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Connecticut","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Georgia","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Hawaii","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Delaware","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Montana","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"North Dakota","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Virginia","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."}],"maxPollsShown":9,"showExitPollPicker":false},"nationalStateClientFetch":{"pollName":"California","lastUpdated":"8 P.M. ET.","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 2 Which has really long text that will porbably wrap","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Which best describes your education? You have: 3","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":0},{"color":"#DE3535","value":0},{"color":"#A99369","value":0},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":0}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Biden","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Trump","color":"DE3535"}],"pollsByState":[{"stateName":"National Presidential","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Arizona","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"California","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Colorado","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Connecticut","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Georgia","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Hawaii","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Delaware","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Montana","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"North Dakota","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Virginia","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."}],"maxPollsShown":9,"showExitPollPicker":true},"statePageDefault":{"pollName":"Colorado","lastUpdated":"8 P.M. ET.","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2 Which has really long text that will porbably wrap","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Which best describes your education? You have:","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":0},{"color":"#DE3535","value":0},{"color":"#A99369","value":0},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":0}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Gender by marital status","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Another different question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"A different question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Some other poll","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"This is a question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Biden","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Trump","color":"DE3535"},{"label":"Hawkins (O)","color":"7A7A7A"}],"pollsByState":null,"maxPollsShown":3},"statePageNoValues":{"pollName":"Colorado","lastUpdated":"8 P.M. ET.","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 2 Which has really long text that will porbably wrap","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 3","percentage":"52%","values":[]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 2","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 3","percentage":"52%","values":[]}]},{"question":"Which best describes your education? You have:","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 2","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 3","percentage":"52%","values":[]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 2","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 3","percentage":"52%","values":[]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 2","percentage":"52%","values":[]},{"label":"Category 3","percentage":"52%","values":[]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Biden","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Trump","color":"DE3535"},{"label":"Hawkins (O)","color":"7A7A7A"}],"pollsByState":null,"maxPollsShown":3},"nationalPageLessMax":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 P.M. ET.","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2 Which has really long text that will porbably wrap","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":0},{"color":"#DE3535","value":0},{"color":"#A99369","value":0},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":0}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Gender by marital status","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Another different question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"A different question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Some other poll","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"This is a question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Biden","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Trump","color":"DE3535"},{"label":"Hawkins (O)","color":"7A7A7A"}],"pollsByState":[{"stateName":"National Presidential","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Arizona","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"California","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Colorado","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Connecticut","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Georgia","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Hawaii","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Delaware","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Montana","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"North Dakota","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Virginia","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."}],"maxPollsShown":9,"showExitPollPicker":true},"nationalPageNoPicker":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 P.M. ET.","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2 Which has really long text that will porbably wrap","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Which best describes your education? You have:","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":0},{"color":"#DE3535","value":0},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":0}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Gender by marital status","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Another different question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"A different question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"Some other poll","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]},{"question":"This is a question","answers":[{"label":"Category 1","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 2","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]},{"label":"Category 3","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25},{"color":"#7A7A7A","value":2}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Biden","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Trump","color":"DE3535"},{"label":"Jorgensen (L)","color":"A99369"},{"label":"Hawkins (O)","color":"7A7A7A"}],"pollsByState":[{"stateName":"National Presidential","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Arizona","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"California","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Colorado","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Connecticut","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Georgia","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Hawaii","pollsOpen":false,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Delaware","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Montana","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"North Dakota","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."},{"stateName":"Virginia","pollsOpen":true,"pollsClose":"8 P.M. ET."}],"maxPollsShown":9,"showExitPollPicker":false},"nationalWithSubsets":{"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"exitPollsNotClosedText":"Come back at 5pm ET for national exit polls questions. Complete results will be available at 8pm ET when polls close.","hideModule":false,"isNational":true,"maxPollsShown":9,"pollName":"National Presidential","resultsNotYetIn":false,"showSectionHeader":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false,"subsets":[{"title":"All voters","code":0,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"72%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"72%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"72%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":56},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":56},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":54},{"color":"#DE3535","value":43}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":27}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"No","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"No","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"77%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"No","percent":"96%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]},{"label":"No","percent":"83%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"83%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":69},{"color":"#DE3535","value":29}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":69},{"color":"#DE3535","value":29}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]},{"label":"No","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"No","percent":"89%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":73}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":24},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":65},{"color":"#DE3535","value":33}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":28},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":29},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":69},{"color":"#DE3535","value":29}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":27},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":7},{"color":"#DE3535","value":90}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":66},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":68},{"color":"#DE3535","value":30}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":24},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":72},{"color":"#DE3535","value":26}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"55%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":27},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":27}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":75},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":26},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":73},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"No","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":30}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"No","percent":"67%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]},{"label":"No","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":73},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":8}]},{"label":"No","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"67%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":28},{"color":"#DE3535","value":71}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":29}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"70%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"70%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"85%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"South","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"West","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}},{"title":"White","code":5,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"No","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"No","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":29},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"96%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"No","percent":"84%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"No","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"No","percent":"91%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":89}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":27},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":44}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"67%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":66},{"color":"#DE3535","value":33}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":28},{"color":"#DE3535","value":71}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":73},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":6},{"color":"#DE3535","value":92}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":66},{"color":"#DE3535","value":33}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":66},{"color":"#DE3535","value":32}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":75},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"67%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":8}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"55%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]},{"label":"No","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"No","percent":"71%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":24},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]},{"label":"No","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"No","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"76%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":8}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"72%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"72%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"84%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"South","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":27},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]},{"label":"West","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}},{"title":"Black","code":6,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":8}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":8}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":8}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"No","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"73%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"86%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"95%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"83%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"79%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"87%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":95},{"color":"#DE3535","value":3}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"86%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":69},{"color":"#DE3535","value":26}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"71%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":96},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":3}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"79%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"82%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"79%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"68%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"82%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":95},{"color":"#DE3535","value":3}]},{"label":"No","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"55%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"No","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"73%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"83%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"78%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"74%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":3}]},{"label":"No","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"85%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"86%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":6}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":95},{"color":"#DE3535","value":3}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":96},{"color":"#DE3535","value":3}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"85%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"South","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"West","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}},{"title":"Hispanic","code":7,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"55%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"55%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":29}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":43}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":54},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":54},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":69},{"color":"#DE3535","value":30}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":68},{"color":"#DE3535","value":32}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":65},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"No","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"82%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"94%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"76%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":72},{"color":"#DE3535","value":27}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"84%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":69}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"55%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"No","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":44}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":29},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"88%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":66},{"color":"#DE3535","value":33}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]},{"label":"South","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"West","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":33}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}},{"title":"Men","code":20,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"74%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"74%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"74%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":32}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"74%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":68},{"color":"#DE3535","value":30}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":32}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":19}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"No","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"No","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"79%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"96%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"No","percent":"82%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"83%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":29},{"color":"#DE3535","value":69}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"No","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":54},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"No","percent":"89%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":8},{"color":"#DE3535","value":91}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":28},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":19}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":65},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":66},{"color":"#DE3535","value":33}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":26},{"color":"#DE3535","value":71}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":27},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":43}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":72},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":8},{"color":"#DE3535","value":89}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":68},{"color":"#DE3535","value":30}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":32}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":27}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":19}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":73}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":54},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":26},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]},{"label":"No","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"No","percent":"68%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":28},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"52%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":9},{"color":"#DE3535","value":89}]},{"label":"No","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":32}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"No","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"71%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":65},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"67%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"67%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"82%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"South","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"West","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}},{"title":"Women","code":21,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"71%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":32}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"71%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"2%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"71%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"71%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":44}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":75},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]},{"label":"No","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"No","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"76%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"95%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":44}]},{"label":"No","percent":"84%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"84%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":24},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":47},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":69}]},{"label":"No","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":54},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]},{"label":"No","percent":"90%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":69}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":26},{"color":"#DE3535","value":73}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":71},{"color":"#DE3535","value":27}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":24},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":75},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":73},{"color":"#DE3535","value":26}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":75},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":6},{"color":"#DE3535","value":92}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":73}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":68},{"color":"#DE3535","value":31}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":72},{"color":"#DE3535","value":26}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":29},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":29},{"color":"#DE3535","value":69}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":28},{"color":"#DE3535","value":70}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":92},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":31}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":73}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":75},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]},{"label":"No","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":69},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":69},{"color":"#DE3535","value":30}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"No","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"43%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"No","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":7}]},{"label":"No","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":74},{"color":"#DE3535","value":25}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":10}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":93},{"color":"#DE3535","value":5}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"73%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"73%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"87%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":52},{"color":"#DE3535","value":47}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":53},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"South","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"West","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}},{"title":"White College Educated","code":45,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"54%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"51%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"No","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"No","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"74%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"96%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"86%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"76%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":9},{"color":"#DE3535","value":91}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]},{"label":"No","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"90%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":26},{"color":"#DE3535","value":73}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":75},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":73},{"color":"#DE3535","value":26}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":56},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":24},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":70},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":56},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":9},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":68},{"color":"#DE3535","value":31}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"55%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":19},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"39%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":67},{"color":"#DE3535","value":33}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":72},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"68%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":21},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":91},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"69%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":23}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"26%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":81},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":64},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]},{"label":"No","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":8},{"color":"#DE3535","value":90}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":24}]},{"label":"No","percent":"69%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":75}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":89},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"68%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":90}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":72},{"color":"#DE3535","value":28}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"No","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":85},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"No","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":86},{"color":"#DE3535","value":13}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":17}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"78%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":89}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":8},{"color":"#DE3535","value":91}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":89}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"21%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"7%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"69%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"69%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"82%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":54}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"South","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":26},{"color":"#DE3535","value":73}]},{"label":"West","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}},{"title":"White No College","code":46,"polls":{"pollName":"National Presidential","lastUpdated":"8 PM ET","polls":[{"question":"Gender","answers":[{"label":"Male","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Female","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Are you:","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"American Indian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Black","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Hispanic/Latino","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Asian","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Race","answers":[{"label":"White","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Non-White","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Sex by race","answers":[{"label":"White men","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"White women","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Black men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Black women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino men","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Latino women","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"All other races","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-29","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]},{"label":"30-44","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"45-64","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-44","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"45+","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"Age","answers":[{"label":"18-24","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":48}]},{"label":"25-29","percent":"6%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"30-39","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"40-49","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"50-64","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"65 or over","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"Never attended college","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Attended college but received no degree","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":60}]},{"label":"Associate's degree (AA or AS)","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"Bachelor's degree (BA or BS)","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"An advanced degree after a bachelor's degree (such as JD, MA, MBA, MD, PhD)","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Education","answers":[{"label":"College graduate","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No college degree","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"Education by race","answers":[{"label":"White college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White non-college graduates","percent":"100%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"Non White college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Non White non-college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Education by Gender among White Voters","answers":[{"label":"White women college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White women non-college graduates","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"White men college graduates","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"White men non-college graduates","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Non-whites","percent":"-1%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:","answers":[{"label":"Democrat","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Republican","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Independent or something else","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"On most political matters, do you consider yourself:","answers":[{"label":"Liberal","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":76},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]},{"label":"Moderate","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":44},{"color":"#DE3535","value":55}]},{"label":"Conservative","percent":"46%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"2021 total family income:","answers":[{"label":"Under $30,000","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"$30,000 - $49,999","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":31},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]},{"label":"$50,000 - $99,999","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":64}]},{"label":"$100,000 - $199,999","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"$200,000 or more","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]}]},{"question":"Are you currently married?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"No","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":41},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"Do you have any children under 18 living in your home?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"No","percent":"60%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"Married with children:","answers":[{"label":"Married with children","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"76%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":62}]}]},{"question":"Parents","answers":[{"label":"Men with children","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":32},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"Women with children","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"Men without children","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Women without children","percent":"32%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]},{"question":"Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"4%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"96%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household belong to a labor union?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]},{"label":"No","percent":"84%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]}]},{"question":"White evangelical or white born-again Christians","answers":[{"label":"White evangelical or white born-again Christian","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"All others","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":45},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]},{"label":"Occasionally","percent":"34%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":27},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"How often do you attend religious services?","answers":[{"label":"Once a week or more or occasionally","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]},{"label":"Never","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"Does anyone in your household own a gun?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]},{"label":"No","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":50},{"color":"#DE3535","value":49}]}]},{"question":"Is this the first time you have ever voted in a midterm election?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"No","percent":"91%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly approve","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":87},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"Somewhat approve","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":20}]},{"label":"Somewhat disapprove","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"Strongly disapprove","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":90}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way Joe Biden is handling his job as president?","answers":[{"label":"Strongly or somewhat approve","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Strongly or somewhat disapprove","percent":"66%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Donald Trump:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"58%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the way things are going in the country today?","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":41}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":66}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent","percent":"8%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Good","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":57},{"color":"#DE3535","value":43}]},{"label":"Not so good","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"Poor","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:","answers":[{"label":"Excellent or good","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]},{"label":"Not so good or poor","percent":"69%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":23},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Compared to two years ago, is your family's financial situation:","answers":[{"label":"Better","percent":"15%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"Worse","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"About the same","percent":"23%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":55},{"color":"#DE3535","value":45}]}]},{"question":"In the last year, has inflation caused you and your family:","answers":[{"label":"A severe hardship","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"A moderate hardship","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":38},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]},{"label":"No hardship at all","percent":"27%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":63},{"color":"#DE3535","value":37}]}]},{"question":"Which ONE of these five issues mattered most in deciding how you voted today:","answers":[{"label":"Inflation","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]},{"label":"Abortion","percent":"18%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]},{"label":"Crime and safety","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]},{"label":"Immigration","percent":"14%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":33},{"color":"#DE3535","value":67}]},{"label":"placeholder","percent":"11%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":49},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal in all cases","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Legal in most cases","percent":"12%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":73},{"color":"#DE3535","value":26}]},{"label":"Illegal in most cases","percent":"41%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Illegal in all cases","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":5},{"color":"#DE3535","value":93}]}]},{"question":"Which comes closest to your position? Abortion should be:","answers":[{"label":"Legal","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":79},{"color":"#DE3535","value":19}]},{"label":"Illegal","percent":"61%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":89}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about the recent Supreme Court decision on abortion that overturned Roe v. Wade:","answers":[{"label":"Enthusiastic","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]},{"label":"Satisfied, but not enthusiastic","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":77}]},{"label":"Dissatisfied, but not angry","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":50}]},{"label":"Angry","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":14}]}]},{"question":"How do you feel about Joe Biden\u2019s plan to cancel some student loan debt?","answers":[{"label":"Approve","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":58},{"color":"#DE3535","value":42}]},{"label":"Disapprove","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":18},{"color":"#DE3535","value":81}]}]},{"question":"Do you support or oppose stricter gun control measures?","answers":[{"label":"Support","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":60},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Oppose","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":15},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"Do you think immigrants to the U.S. today do more to:","answers":[{"label":"Help the country","percent":"37%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":62},{"color":"#DE3535","value":36}]},{"label":"Hurt the country","percent":"59%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":22},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of inflation?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"49%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":38}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of abortion?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":65},{"color":"#DE3535","value":31}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of crime?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"29%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":77},{"color":"#DE3535","value":22}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"65%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":76}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of immigration?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":90},{"color":"#DE3535","value":9}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]}]},{"question":"Who do you trust more to handle the issue of placeholder?","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"35%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":80},{"color":"#DE3535","value":18}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"62%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that the attack on the U.S. Capitol on January 6, 2021 represents:","answers":[{"label":"A major problem","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"A minor problem","percent":"24%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":51},{"color":"#DE3535","value":46}]},{"label":"Not a problem","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":17},{"color":"#DE3535","value":79}]}]},{"question":"In the 2020 election for president, did you vote for:","answers":[{"label":"Joe Biden (Dem)","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"Donald Trump (Rep)","percent":"57%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]},{"label":"Other","percent":"3%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Did not vote","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"Do you think that Joe Biden legitimately won the presidency in 2020?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"44%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":63},{"color":"#DE3535","value":35}]},{"label":"No","percent":"50%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":84}]}]},{"question":"How confident are you that elections in your state are being conducted fairly and accurately?","answers":[{"label":"Very confident","percent":"19%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":61},{"color":"#DE3535","value":39}]},{"label":"Somewhat confident","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":52}]},{"label":"Not very confident","percent":"16%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":25},{"color":"#DE3535","value":74}]},{"label":"Not at all confident","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":82}]}]},{"question":"Would you like to see Joe Biden run for president in 2024?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":78},{"color":"#DE3535","value":21}]},{"label":"No","percent":"74%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":26},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Democratic Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"30%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":82},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"64%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":16},{"color":"#DE3535","value":80}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of the Republican Party:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"56%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":13},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"40%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":72},{"color":"#DE3535","value":26}]}]},{"question":"Is the Democratic party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"53%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":9},{"color":"#DE3535","value":90}]},{"label":"No","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":65},{"color":"#DE3535","value":34}]}]},{"question":"Is the Republican party too extreme?","answers":[{"label":"Yes","percent":"28%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":11}]},{"label":"No","percent":"67%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":11},{"color":"#DE3535","value":88}]}]},{"question":"Would you rather see the U.S. House of Representatives controlled by:","answers":[{"label":"The Democratic Party","percent":"31%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":83},{"color":"#DE3535","value":16}]},{"label":"The Republican Party","percent":"63%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":86}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Nancy Pelosi:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":84},{"color":"#DE3535","value":15}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":20},{"color":"#DE3535","value":78}]}]},{"question":"Is your opinion of Kevin McCarthy:","answers":[{"label":"Favorable","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":10},{"color":"#DE3535","value":87}]},{"label":"Unfavorable","percent":"48%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":59},{"color":"#DE3535","value":40}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Joe Biden","percent":"13%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":88},{"color":"#DE3535","value":12}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Joe Biden","percent":"38%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":14},{"color":"#DE3535","value":83}]},{"label":"Joe Biden was not a factor","percent":"45%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":42},{"color":"#DE3535","value":57}]}]},{"question":"Was one reason for your vote for U.S. House today:","answers":[{"label":"To express support for Donald Trump","percent":"36%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":12},{"color":"#DE3535","value":85}]},{"label":"To express opposition to Donald Trump","percent":"17%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":94},{"color":"#DE3535","value":4}]},{"label":"Donald Trump was not a factor","percent":"42%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":34},{"color":"#DE3535","value":65}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last few days","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last week","percent":"5%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"In the last month","percent":"10%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":48},{"color":"#DE3535","value":51}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last month","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":43},{"color":"#DE3535","value":56}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"75%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":36},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]}]},{"question":"When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the U.S. House election?","answers":[{"label":"In the last week","percent":"9%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":-1},{"color":"#DE3535","value":-1}]},{"label":"Before that","percent":"85%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]}]},{"question":"Area","answers":[{"label":"City over 50,000","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":35},{"color":"#DE3535","value":63}]},{"label":"Suburbs","percent":"47%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":39},{"color":"#DE3535","value":59}]},{"label":"Small city and Rural","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":30},{"color":"#DE3535","value":68}]}]},{"question":"National Region","answers":[{"label":"East","percent":"20%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":46},{"color":"#DE3535","value":53}]},{"label":"Midwest","percent":"25%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":37},{"color":"#DE3535","value":61}]},{"label":"South","percent":"33%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":27},{"color":"#DE3535","value":72}]},{"label":"West","percent":"22%","values":[{"color":"#0471E6","value":40},{"color":"#DE3535","value":58}]}]}],"candidates":[{"label":"Dem","color":"0471E6"},{"label":"Rep","color":"DE3535"}],"maxPollsShown":9,"resultsNotYetIn":false,"showPollsNotClosedText":false}}],"description":null,"lastUpdated":null,"linkText":null,"linkUrl":null,"pollsByState":[],"showExitPollPicker":false,"title":"Exit Polls"}}`),{nationalPageDefault:Me,nationalStateClientFetch:ke,statePageDefault:Re}=De,K=Pe;var r=o.createElement;const{nationalPageDefault:Ce,statePageDefault:Se,nationalWithSubsets:re}=De,We={component:K,title:"Features/Exit Polls/2022/Exit Polls Module",parameters:{design:{type:"figma",url:"https://www.figma.com/file/6DP0s7gYs5wwWf0bvaKMSj/Exit-Polls?node-id=181%3A34000&t=JvBczEEr99HIEd5P-0"},status:{type:"deprecated"}}},he=()=>r("div",null,r("div",{className:"fixed top0 w-100 z-max"},r("div",{style:{height:"80px"},className:"bg-midnight-blue"}),r("div",{style:{height:"50px",borderBottom:"solid 1px #ccc"},className:"bg-white"})),r("div",{style:{marginTop:"150px"}},r(K,(0,b.default)({},Ce,{hideModule:!1}))));he.displayName="NationalPage";const ve=()=>r("div",null,r("div",{className:"fixed top0 w-100 z-max"},r("div",{style:{height:"80px"},className:"bg-midnight-blue"}),r("div",{style:{height:"50px",borderBottom:"solid 1px #ccc"},className:"bg-white"})),r("div",{style:{marginTop:"150px"}},r(K,(0,b.default)({},Se,{hideModule:!1}))));ve.displayName="StatePage",ve.parameters={design:{type:"figma",url:"https://www.figma.com/file/6DP0s7gYs5wwWf0bvaKMSj/Exit-Polls?node-id=181%3A28619&t=JvBczEEr99HIEd5P-0"}};const ye=()=>{const{0:c,1:h}=(0,o.useState)(0),p=re.subsets.find(N=>N.code===c)?.polls??[];return r("div",null,r("div",{className:"fixed top0 w-100 z-max"},r("div",{style:{height:"80px"},className:"bg-midnight-blue"}),r("div",{style:{height:"50px",borderBottom:"solid 1px #ccc"},className:"bg-white"})),r("div",{style:{marginTop:"150px"}},r(K,(0,b.default)({},p,{activeSubset:c,subsets:re.subsets,onSubsetChange:h,hideModule:!1,hideNegativeValues:!0}))))};ye.displayName="NationalExitPollSubsets";const me=()=>{const{0:c,1:h}=(0,o.useState)(5),p=re.subsets.find(N=>N.code===c)?.polls??[];return r("div",null,r("div",{className:"fixed top0 w-100 z-max"},r("div",{style:{height:"80px"},className:"bg-midnight-blue"}),r("div",{style:{height:"50px",borderBottom:"solid 1px #ccc"},className:"bg-white"})),r("div",{style:{marginTop:"150px"}},r(K,(0,b.default)({},p,{activeSubset:c,subsets:re.subsets,onSubsetChange:h,hideModule:!1,hideNegativeValues:!0}))))};me.displayName="SubsetsWithActiveDemographic";const Te=["NationalPage","StatePage","NationalExitPollSubsets","SubsetsWithActiveDemographic"]},"./components/HorizontalLabeledStackedBarChart/2022/index.js":(ee,v,l)=>{l.r(v),l.d(v,{ChartPropTypes:()=>k.default,default:()=>H});var b=l("./node_modules/styled-jsx/style.js"),o=l.n(b),s=l("./node_modules/next/dist/compiled/react/index.js"),w=l("./node_modules/classnames/index.js"),e=l.n(w),i=l("./node_modules/react-i18next/dist/es/index.js"),B=l("./node_modules/prop-types/index.js"),t=l.n(B),x=l("./components/hooks/useWindowSize.js"),u=s.createElement;const I=({value:g,color:S,height:d,textSize:f,isExitPolls:O,isTextAlignRight:a,hasSmallValueTextShadow:U,hideSmallBarText:P,hideText:$})=>{const W=`${g}%`,{width:le}=(0,x.default)(),j=le<758;return u(s.Fragment,null,u(o(),{id:"2683735065",dynamic:[d,d,f]},[`.lh-16{line-height:${d};}`,`.labeled-bar{position:relative;margin-right:2px;height:${d};}`,".labeled-bar:last-child{margin-right:0;}",`.labeled-bar span{font-size:${f};}`,".shadow{text-shadow: -1px -1px 0 #000, 0 -1px 0 #000, 1px -1px 0 #000, 1px 0 0 #000, 1px 1px 0 #000, 0 1px 0 #000, -1px 1px 0 #000, -1px 0 0 #000;z-index:1;}"]),u(o(),{id:"2578052038",dynamic:[S]},[`.labeled-bar.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector{background-color:${S};}`,".exit-poll-percent.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector{-webkit-letter-spacing:0.5px;-moz-letter-spacing:0.5px;-ms-letter-spacing:0.5px;letter-spacing:0.5px;}"]),u("div",{"data-testid":"bar-chart--results-bar",style:{width:W},className:o().dynamic([["2683735065",[d,d,f]],["2578052038",[S]]])+" "+(e()("labeled-bar df white",{"justify-center justify-start-m":g<=10&&P,"justify-end":a})||"")},u("span",{className:o().dynamic([["2683735065",[d,d,f]],["2578052038",[S]]])+" "+(e()("lh-16",{"dn db-m":g<=10&&P,"founders-txt":!O,"founders-cond exit-poll-percent mh2":O,db:g>10,dn:$,ml1:!O,shadow:U&&(g<=7||j&&g<=16)})||"")},W)))};I.propTypes={value:t().number,color:t().string,height:t().string,isTextAlignRight:t().bool,hasSmallValueTextShadow:t().bool,hideSmallBarText:t().bool,hideText:t().bool,textSize:t().string},I.defaultProps={value:null,color:"",isTextAlignRight:!1,hasSmallValueTextShadow:!1,hideSmallBarText:!0,hideText:!1,height:"16px",textSize:"12px"};const q=I;var M=l("./components/HorizontalLabeledStackedBarChart/Legend.js"),k=l("./components/HorizontalLabeledStackedBarChart/Chart.propsShape.js"),E=s.createElement;const R=({values:g,showLegend:S,t:d,resultsNotYetIn:f,showResultsNotInLabel:O,height:a,textSize:U,isExitPolls:P,isTwoBarSplit:$,hasSmallValueTextShadow:W,hideSmallBarText:le})=>{const j=g.filter(T=>T.value>0),F=j.length===0,se=P&&j.length>2;return E(s.Fragment,null,E(o(),{id:"3389105416",dynamic:[a,a]},[`.lh-16.__jsx-style-dynamic-selector{line-height:${a};min-height:${a};}`]),E("figure",{className:o().dynamic([["3389105416",[a,a]]])+" "+(e()("mh0 mb0",{mt2:P,mt3:!P})||"")},E("div",{className:o().dynamic([["3389105416",[a,a]]])+" "+(e()("df w-100 bg-wild-sand",{"justify-between":$})||"")},f&&E("div",{"data-testid":"bar-chart--results-not-in",className:o().dynamic([["3389105416",[a,a]]])+" mh1 f2 founders-mono f2 lh-16 gray-100"},O&&d("Results not yet available")),!f&&F&&E("div",{"data-testid":"bar-chart--invalid",className:o().dynamic([["3389105416",[a,a]]])+" mh1 f2 founders-mono f2 lh-16 gray-100"},d("polls.notEnoughData")),!F&&j.map((T,oe)=>E(q,{key:T.value+T.color,value:T.value,color:T.color,height:a,textSize:U,hasSmallValueTextShadow:W,hideSmallBarText:le,isTextAlignRight:($||se)&&oe===1,isExitPolls:P,hideText:se&&oe>1}))),E(M.default,{values:g,showLegend:S})))};R.propTypes=k.default,R.defaultProps={hasSmallValueTextShadow:!1,hideSmallBarText:!0,height:"16px",isExitPolls:!1,isTwoBarSplit:!1,resultsNotYetIn:!1,showLegend:!0,showResultsNotInLabel:!1,textSize:"12px",values:[]};const H=(0,i.withTranslation)()(R)},"./components/LinklessButton.js":(ee,v,l)=>{l.r(v),l.d(v,{default:()=>u});var b=l("./node_modules/styled-jsx/style.js"),o=l.n(b),s=l("./node_modules/next/dist/compiled/react/index.js"),w=l("./node_modules/prop-types/index.js"),e=l.n(w),i=l("./node_modules/classnames/index.js"),B=l.n(i),t=s.createElement;const x=({children:I,classes:q,onClick:M,isBlock:k})=>{const{0:E,1:R}=(0,s.useState)(!1),z=B()({db:k,dib:!k},"button-press founders-cond lh-none f4 fw6 ttu",{"clear-blue bg-white":!E,"white bg-clear-blue":E},q);return t(s.Fragment,null,t(o(),{id:"1765211304"},[".button-press.jsx-1765211304{border:1px solid #3061ff;-webkit-transition:background-position ease 0.2s;transition:background-position ease 0.2s;background-position:-600px 0;background-repeat:no-repeat;background-image:linear-gradient(35deg,#3061ff 50%,transparent 0);cursor:pointer;}",".button-press.jsx-1765211304:hover{background-size:325% 100%;background-position:0 0;color:#fff;}"]),t("button",{type:"button","data-testid":"button-press",onClick:H=>{R(!E),M(H)},className:"jsx-1765211304 "+(z||"")},I))};x.propTypes={isBlock:e().bool,onClick:e().func.isRequired},x.defaultProps={isBlock:!1};const u=x},"./components/hooks/useWindowSize.js":(ee,v,l)=>{l.r(v),l.d(v,{default:()=>e});var b=l("./node_modules/next/dist/compiled/react/index.js"),o=l("./node_modules/lodash.debounce/index.js"),s=l.n(o);function w({trailing:i=!1}={}){const{0:B,1:t}=(0,b.useState)({width:void 0,height:void 0});return(0,b.useEffect)(()=>{const x={leading:!0,trailing:i},u=s()(()=>{t({width:window.innerWidth,height:window.innerHeight})},200,x);return window.addEventListener("resize",u),u(),()=>window.removeEventListener("resize",u)},[]),B}const e=w},"./helpers/color.js":(ee,v,l)=>{l.r(v),l.d(v,{convertToHex:()=>b,hexToRgb:()=>o});function b(s){return s&&(s.startsWith("#")?s.toLowerCase():`#${s.replace("bg-","")}`.toLowerCase())}function o(s){const w=s.replace("#","");return(w.length===3?w.split("").map(i=>`${i}${i}`):w.split(/(\w{2})/).filter(Boolean)).map(i=>parseInt(i,16)).join(",")}}}]);
